Hi, my name's Erie from Plastic Labs. If
you're using Hermes agent and you want
to give its memory a massive upgrade,
you should enable Honcho.
Honcho is an AI native memory framework
that can unify all of your context
across sessions. Not only does it store
your context, but it uses a custom model
to reason about said context to get to
know you better than any other memory
framework that exists.
Okay, so here's what to do.
First, you're going to grab your API key
from app.honcho.dev.
Go to the API keys tab.
Create.
We're going to name it Hermes.
Make sure to copy it to your clipboard
and save it for just a minute later.
Next, we're going to go back to Hermes,
make sure it's updated. So, you run
Hermes update.
And you should now have access to the
Honcho CLI. And from there, we run
Hermes Honcho setup.
Here some prompts will appear. It asks
you for your API key. Paste and done.
Your name, which is up here. That's how
Honcho identifies you. My name is Erie,
so there we go. Workspace ID, default to
Hermes. And from here, we're going to
just keep the defaults for everything.
Memory mode, hybrid.
Write frequency, async. Recall mode,
hybrid.
Session strategy, per session. Now, we
boot up Hermes and you're ready to go
with Honcho. Beyond Hermes, Honcho can
integrate with Open Claw, Claude Code,
Cursor, and more. There's $100 of free
credits to start. Visit honcho.dev for
more information.